homesnap.com 2015-06-14

# Privacy Policy :: Homesnap

Homesnap is committed to protecting your privacy. We will never send spam to you, nor will we sell or distribute your email address or other personal information to unaffiliated parties without your consent. We have put in place suitable, industry-standard physical, electronic and managerial procedures to keep safe and secure any information we may collect from our users. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, which applies to the use of [www.homesnap.com](http://www.homesnap.com/) and our mobile apps. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [info@homesnap.com](mailto:info@homesnap.com). Our corporate address is: Sawbuck Realty, Inc., d/b/a Homesnap, 4733 Bethesda Avenue Suite 650 Bethesda, MD 20814. 

## Information We Collect

Users may view active listings on our site and review the entire site’s content without providing any personal information. If a user wishes to set up email alerts or view sold and “under contract” listings, registration is required. Registration consists of providing an email address and creating a password, which information is kept private consistent with this policy.

Our web server automatically recognizes only the user’s domain name, unless the user has previously chosen to register, in which case it will also recognize the user’s email address. In order to improve our services and enhance the user’s experience on our site, we collect information about what pages consumers access or visit.

We use “cookies” in a manner similar to most other Web sites. A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual and to remember information about your preferences, which can enhance and improve your user experience. For this reason, most web browsers automatically accept cookies, however you typically may modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer.

Various brokers/agents, lenders and escrow/settlement companies to whom we may refer you each may have their own privacy policies governing how they handle any of your personally identifiable information. Homesnap accepts no responsibility or liability for third party privacy policies or the actions of any third party with respect to your personally identifiable information.

## Fair Housing Notice 

"We are pledged to the letter and spirit of U.S. policy for the achievement of equal housing opportunity throughout the nation. We encourage and support an affirmative advertising and marketing program in which there are no barriers to obtaining housing because of race, color, religion, sex, handicap, familial status, or national origin."

For more information, please visit the [Office of Fair Housing and Equal Opportunity (FHEO)](http://www.hud.gov/offices/fheo/index.cfm).
